var questions=[
    {
        num : 1,
        question : "",
        answer : "Kazakhstan",
        options : [
            "Colombia",
            "Kazakhstan",
            "Argentina",
            "Ecuador",
        ]
    },
    {
    num : 2,
    question : "",
    answer : "Portugal",
    options : [
        "Panama",
        "Nicaragua",
        "Paraguay",
        "Portugal",
    ]
},
{
    num : 3,
    question : "",
    answer : "Azerbaijan",
    options : [
        "Barbados",
        "Guadeloupe (France)",
        "Belize",
        "Azerbaijan",
    ]
},
{
    num : 4,
    question : "",
    answer : "Hungary",
    options : [
        "Hungary",
        "Dominica",
        "Anguilla (UK)",
        "Ireland",
    ]
},
{
    num : 5,
    question : "",
    answer : "Belarus",
    options : [
        "Bermuda",
        "Belarus",
        "Dominica",
        "Antigua and Barbuda",
    ]
},
{
    num : 6,
    question : "",
    answer : "Serbia",
    options : [
        "Tonga",
        "Oceania Countries",
        "Kiribati",
        "Serbia",
    ]
},
{
    num : 7,
    question : "",
    answer : "Denmark",
    options : [
        "Denmark",
        "Palau",
        "Tuvalu",
        "Nauru",
    ]
},
{
    num : 8,
    question : "",
    answer : "Finland",
    options : [
        "Belarus",
        "Austria",
        "Switzerland",
        "Finland",
    ]
},
{
    num : 9,
    question : "",
    answer : "Norway",
    options : [
        "Norfolk Island",
        "Vatican City",
        "Norway",
        "San Marino",
    ]
},
{
    num : 10,
    question : "",
    answer : "Slovakia",
    options : [
        "Australia",
        "Western New Guinea",
        "Wallis and Futuna",
        "Slovakia",
    ]
},
{
    num : 11,
    question : "",
    answer : "Croatia",
    options : [
        "Latvia",
        "Albania",
        "Croatia",
        "Kosovo",
    ]
},
{
    num : 12,
    question : "",
    answer : "Albania",
    options : [
        "North Macedonia",
        "Albania",
        "American Samoa ",
        "Montenegro",
    ]
},
{
    num : 13,
    question : "",
    answer : "Moldova",
    options : [
        "Isle of Man",
        "Faroe Islands",
        "Monaco",
        "Moldova",
    ]
},
{
    num : 14,
    question : "",
    answer : "Slovenia",
    options : [
        "Slovenia",
        "Latvia",
        "Kosovo",
        "Cyprus",
    ]
},
{
    num : 15,
    question : "",
    answer : "Latvia",
    options : [
        "Latvia",
        "Monaco",
        "Liechtenstein",
        "San Marino",
    ]
},
{
    num : 16,
    question : "",
    answer : "Kosovo",
    options : [
        "Croatia",
        "Bulgaria",
        "Kosovo",
        "Serbia",
    ]
},
{
    num : 17,
    question : "",
    answer : "Estonia",
    options : [
        "Luxembourg",
        "Estonia",
        "Montenegro",
        "Malta",
    ]
},
  {
    num : 18,
    question : "",
    answer : "Cyprus",
    options : [
        "Lithuania",
        "Armenia",
        "Cyprus",
        "Georgia",
    ]
},
  {
    num : 19,
    question : "",
    answer : "Jersey",
    options : [
        "Latvia",
        "Estonia",
        "Kosovo",
        "Jersey",
    ]
},
{
    num : 20,
    question : "",
    answer : "Gibraltar",
    options : [
        "Azerbaijan",
        "Bulgaria",
        "Croatia",
        "Gibraltar",
    ]
}
];